plus he came to Las Vegas hoping to
advance his career but instead decided
to find a new one why so many are
choosing to change jobs
and we are watching out for you this is
News smia 5 with Malia Silva and Gerard
romallo
good evening thanks for joining us with
the challenging economy dragging on many
Valley residents are making the decision
to change careers now for some that
change is coming later in life this Dan
ball has the story of a 56-year-old
Henderson man who moved to the valley
thinking he'd find work in one trade but
is now taking his career in a whole new
Direction and I didn't want him to be
sitting at home and worrying about you
know what what's next when rafy and
aroxy Dean moved to Las Vegas 2 years
ago Rie thought it would be easy to find
a job when we thought of moving to Las
Vegas we said okay we do the move so we
got to start basically over and I
thought I'll find the same thing I
continue over here and uh it wasn't easy
at 56 years old rafy spent most of his
life in two different career Fields I
was a i mass communications degree work
in advertising marketing I switched
completely when I came to La went into
manufacturing and then now it's another
phase of life so rafy's wife made a
suggestion when I suggested he thought
about it for a day or so and came back
and he thought it was a good idea yeah I
said just go for it just 2 weeks ago uh
Ary turns around and says rafy why don't
you go to Real Estate I thought it would
be an ideal thing to go for him because
he's a people's person the new career
move meant rafie would have to go back
to school he's a quick learner I'm
telling you he's doing real good in
school I have 45 hours of real estate
and 45 hours of law including 18 hours
of
NADA and so in one month I'll be ready
to take the exam but in this volatile
real estate market who in their right
minds want to get into the biz now raie
says he's up for the challenge you have
to have a good attitude of what you got
to do my goal obviously is to ASAP get
my live license and be out there selling
homes for the thousands of Valley
residents out of work rafy has this
advice you have to be flexible you have
to be open-minded don't say this is what
I studied and this is the only thing I'm
going to look look at what other
opportunities are there that you can use
your
knowledge to divert what uh goes to
another Direction don't be stuck on one
thing no matter what the ages in the
Seven Hills Anthem area Dan ball news
three yeah good advice Ry is attending
his classes now in Henderson at the
credential Americana group and hopes to
take the state exam by September